继续吧，改改你的名字。不，不是永久改，也不是法律上改。
go on, change your name. No, not permanently or legally. But get
而是要习惯用一种不同于你一辈子以来的方式说自己的名字。
comfortable with saying your own name differently than you have for your entire
这可能会让你觉得奇怪、不真实、超现实，甚至只是傻，
life. It may feel weird, unreal, surreal, or just plain dumb, but it's an invaluable
但这是非常有价值的心理练习。每次到一个新国家，我的第一件事
mental exercise. Every time I landed in a new country, my first order of business
就是弄清楚我是谁，或者至少弄清楚我的名字该怎么发音。
was to find out who I was, or at least how my name was pronounced. I went from
Madrid, Me llamo Anita, to Paris, Je m 'appelle Annie, to Tokyo, Watashi wa Annie
desu。放下包袱。对很多人来说，美式口音带着
desu. Drop the baggage. For a lot of people, the American accent comes with a
很多情绪包袱：美国人大声、情绪不成熟、
lot of emotional baggage. Americans are loud, emotionally immature,
对像你这样受过教育、见识复杂的人来说，这可能会让你感到冲突。
unsophisticated. It may be conflicting for an educated sophisticate such as yourself
但你需要融入并被听懂，所以放下包袱。
to work towards actually sounding like this. But you need to fit in and be
理解，所以放下包袱。只专注于纯粹的声音。
understood, so drop off the baggage. Just focus on the pure sounds." Emotional
对特定声音的情感投入。一位西班牙语口音很明显的男士，
Investment in Particular Sounds A man with a distinctly Spanish accent had trouble
他学会了 iPad 里的 æ 音，但没有
distinguishing iPod from iPad. He learned the ass sound for iPad, but didn't
把这个音推广到 cat、laugh、dance 等其他词里。
extrapolate that sound to other words such as cat, laugh, or dance. It would be
他根本不知道该用到哪里。
natural to think that he simply didn't know where to use it. But surprisingly,
当被问到为什么不用这个 æ 音时，他笑着回答说，
when asked why he didn't use the ass sound, he laughingly responded, Some
人们对自己的发音有很强的认同，
people have a strong identification with their pronunciation, considering it part
他们可能拒绝某一个声音，也可能拒绝整个口音。
of their identity or personal brand. They may reject a single sound or the entire
除非变化源自内心，否则，口音不会根植，
accent. Unless the change wells from within, the accent won't take root and
成为他们真正的一部分。
become a true part of them.